NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NYSUT: Nassau Community College Federation of Teachers through Tompkins Cortland Community College Faculty Association (Box 398)
  - Tompkins Cortland Community College and TC3 Faculty Association, 1995-1998 (Box 398, Folder 35)
- School Districts: Addison Central through Edwards-Knox Central (Box 399)
  - Addison Central School District (Box 399, Folder 1)
  - Adirondack Community College (Box 399, Folder 2)
  - Afton Central School District (Box 399, Folder 3)
  - Allegany Central School District (Box 399, Folder 4)
  - Allegany-Limestone Central School District (Box 399, Folder 5)
  - Andover Central School (Box 399, Folder 6)
  - Arkport Central School District (Box 399, Folder 7)
  - Avon Central School District (Box 399, Folder 8)
  - Baldwinsville Central School District (Box 399, Folder 9)
  - Beacon City School District (Box 399, Folder 10)
  - Bemus Point Central School District (Box 399, Folder 11)
  - Bethlehem Central School District (Box 399, Folder 12)
  - Bolivar Central School District (Box 399, Folder 13)
  - Bradford Central School District (Box 399, Folder 14)
  - Brookfield Central School Teachers' Assoc. (Box 399, Folder 15)
  - Broome County Community College (Box 399, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Board of Education (Box 399, Folder 17)
  - Canaseraga Central School District (Box 399, Folder 18)
  - Canisteo Central School District (Box 399, Folder 19)
  - Cattaraugus-Allegany-Erie-Wyoming Counties BOCES (Box 399, Folder 20)
  - Cayuga County Community College (Box 399, Folder 21)
  - Chatham Central School Teachers' Assoc. (Box 399, Folder 22)
  - Chautaugua-Cattarangus BOCES (Box 399, Folder 23)
  - Churchville-Chili Board of Education (Box 399, Folder 24)
  - Clarkstown Central School District (Box 399, Folder 25)
  - Clymer Central School District (Box 399, Folder 26)
  - Cooperstown Central School District (Box 399, Folder 27)
  - Coxsackie-Athens Central School District (Box 399, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Central School District (Box 399, Folder 29)
  - deer Park Teachers' Assoc. (Box 399, Folder 30)
  - Delaware Academy and Central School (Box 399, Folder 31)
  - Delaware, Chenango, Madison and Otsego Co. Sole Supervisory District (Box 399, Folder 32)
  - Delhi Central School District (Box 399, Folder 33)
  - Detroiter Faculty Assoc. (Box 399, Folder 34)
  - Downsville Central School District (Box 399, Folder 35)
  - Dryden Central School District (Box 399, Folder 36)
  - East Rampo Central School District (Box 399, Folder 37)
  - Edwards-Know Teachers' Assoc. (Box 399, Folder 38)
- School Districts: Elmira City through Lansing Central (Box 400)
  - Elmira City School District (Box 400, Folder 1)
  - Elmira-Heights Central School District (Box 400, Folder 2)
  - Erie II-Chautauqua-Cattaraugus BOCES (Box 400, Folder 3)
  - Fabius-Pompey Central School District (Box 400, Folder 4)
  - Fairport Central School District (Box 400, Folder 5)
  - Fillmore Central School Board (Box 400, Folder 6)
  - Franklin Central School (Box 400, Folder 7)
  - Fulton-Montgomery Community College (Box 400, Folder 8)
  - Genesee Educational Assoc. (Box 400, Folder 9)
  - Geneva City School District (Box 400, Folder 10)
  - Gloversville Enlarged City School District (Box 400, Folder 11)
  - Greece Central School District (Box 400, Folder 12)
  - Greene Central School District (Box 400, Folder 13)
  - Groton Central School (Box 400, Folder 14)
  - Hammondsport Central School (Box 400, Folder 15)
  - Hancock Central School District (Box 400, Folder 16)
  - Hempstead Union Tree School District (Box 400, Folder 17)
  - Hinsdale Central School District (Box 400, Folder 18)
  - Homer Central School District (Box 400, Folder 19)
  - Hornell City School District (Box 400, Folder 20)
  - Hudson Valley Community College (Box 400, Folder 21)
  - Ithaca City School District (Box 400, Folder 22)
  - Jamestown Public Schools (Box 400, Folder 23)
  - Jasper Central School (Box 400, Folder 24)
  - Jasper-Troupsburg Central School District (Box 400, Folder 25)
  - Jefferson Central School District (Box 400, Folder 26)
  - Johnson City School District (Box 400, Folder 27)
  - Kendall Central School District (Box 400, Folder 28)
  - Kenmore-Town of Tonawanda Union Free School District (Box 400, Folder 29)
  - Keshequa Central Teachers Assoc. (Box 400, Folder 30)
  - Lackawanna City School District (Box 400, Folder 31)
  - La Fayette Teachers' Assoc. (Box 400, Folder 32)
  - Lansing Central School District (Box 400, Folder 33)
- School Districts: Letchworth Central through South Kortright Central (Box 401)
  - Letchworth Central School District (Box 401, Folder 1)
  - Liverpool Central School District (Box 401, Folder 2)
  - Maine-Endwell Central School District (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - Marathon Central School District (Box 401, Folder 4)
  - Margaretville School District (Box 401, Folder 5)
  - McGraw Central School District (Box 401, Folder 6)
  - Milford Central School District (Box 401, Folder 7)
  - Monroe and Orleans BOCES (Box 401, Folder 8)
  - Morris Education Association (Box 401, Folder 9)
  - Morrisville-Eaton Central School District (Box 401, Folder 10)
  - Mount Markham Central School (Box 401, Folder 11)
  - Mount Morris Central School District (Box 401, Folder 12)
  - Niagara Community College (Box 401, Folder 13)
  - Niskayuna Central School District (Box 401, Folder 14)
  - North County Community College (Box 401, Folder 15)
  - Norwich City School District (Box 401, Folder 16)
  - Odessa-Montour Central School District (Box 401, Folder 17)
  - Olean City School District (Box 401, Folder 18)
  - Oneonta City School District (Box 401, Folder 19)
  - Otsego-Northern Catskills Teachers' Assoc. (Box 401, Folder 20)
  - Oxford Academy and Central School (Box 401, Folder 21)
  - Panama Central School Board of Education (Box 401, Folder 22)
  - Pawling Central School District (Box 401, Folder 23)
  - Pearl River Board of Education (Box 401, Folder 24)
  - Penn Yan Central School District (Box 401, Folder 25)
  - Plainview-Old Bethpage Central School District (Box 401, Folder 26)
  - Prattsburg Central School District (Box 401, Folder 27)
  - Ramapo Central School District (Box 401, Folder 28)
  - Ripley Central School District (Box 401, Folder 29)
  - Sackets Harbor Central School Teachers' Assoc. (Box 401, Folder 30)
  - Salamanca City School District (Box 401, Folder 31)
  - Sandy Creek Central School (Box 401, Folder 32)
  - Schenectady County Community College (Box 401, Folder 33)
  - Schuyler, Chemung, Tioga BOCES (Box 401, Folder 34)
  - Scio Central School District (Box 401, Folder 35)
  - Sewanhaka Central School District (Box 401, Folder 36)
  - Sherburne-Earlville Teachers' Assoc. (Box 401, Folder 37)
  - Sodus Central School District (Box 401, Folder 38)
  - South Jefferson Central School District (Box 401, Folder 39)
  - South Kortright Central School (Box 401, Folder 40)
- School Districts: Southwestern Central through Wyoming Central (Box 402)
  - Southwestern Central School District (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - Stamford Central School District (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Steuben-Allegany Board of Cooperative (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Stockbridge Valley Central School (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Susquehanna Valley Central School District (Box 402, Folder 5)
  - Tioga Central School District (Box 402, Folder 6)
  - Tompkins-Seneca-Tioga BOCES (Box 402, Folder 7)
  - Trumansburg Central School District (Box 402, Folder 8)
  - Unatego District (Box 402, Folder 9)
  - Vestal Central School District (Box 402, Folder 10)
  - Warsaw Central School District (Box 402, Folder 11)
  - Waterloo Central School District (Box 402, Folder 12)
  - Waverly Central School District (Box 402, Folder 13)
  - Wayland Central School (Box 402, Folder 14)
  - Wayne Central School District (Box 402, Folder 15)
  - Wellsville Central School District (Box 402, Folder 16)
  - Westfield Central School (Box 402, Folder 17)
  - Wolcott Central School District (Box 402, Folder 18)
  - Wyandanch Union Free School District (Box 402, Folder 19)
  - Wyoming Central School District (Box 402, Folder 20)
- PERB #1 (Box 403)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #1 (Box 403, Folder 1)
- PERB #2 (Box 404)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #2 (Box 404, Folder 1)
- PERB #3 (Box 405)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #3 (Box 405, Folder 1)
- PERB #4 (Box 406)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #4 (Box 406, Folder 1)
- PERB #5 (Box 407)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #5 (Box 407, Folder 1)
- PERB #6 (Box 408)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #6 (Box 408, Folder 1)
- PERB #7 (Box 409)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #7 (Box 409, Folder 1)
- PERB #8 (Box 410)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #8 (Box 410, Folder 1)
- PERB CONTRACTS #9 -- 2005 & Cumulative index (Box 411)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #9 (Box 411, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #10 (Box 412)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #10 (Box 412, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #10 (Box 413)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #10 (Box 413, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #11 (Box 414)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #11 (Box 414, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #11 (Box 415)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #11 (Box 415, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #12 (Box 416)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #12 (Box 416, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #12 (Box 417)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #12 (Box 417, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #13 (Box 418)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #13 (Box 418, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #13 (Box 419)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #13 (Box 419, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #14 (Box 420)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #14 (Box 420, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #15 (Box 421)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #15 (Box 421, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #16 (Box 422)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #16 (Box 422, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #16 & Index (Box 423)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #16 (Box 423, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #17 (Box 424)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #17 (Box 424, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #18 - disc 1 of 2 (Box 425)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #18 (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #18 (Box 425, Folder 2)
  - PERB Contracts Disk #20 (Box 425, Folder 3)
- NYS PERB Scanned contracts #18 - disc 2 of 2 (Box 426)
- NYS PERB Contracts, 10/11-01/12 -- #20 (Box 427)
- NYS PERB Contracts - 2/12-8/12 -- #21 (Box 428)
- NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 22 -- 9/12-12/12 (Box 429)
  - NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 22: 9/12-12/12, 2012 (Box 429, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 24 -- 06/13-01/14 (Box 430)
  - NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 24: 06/13-01/14, 2013-2014 (Box 430, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 23 -- 12/28/12-6/3/13 (Box 431)
  - NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 23: 12/28/12-6/3/13, 2012-2013 (Box 431, Folder 1)
- NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 25 - 02/14-08/14 (Box 432)
- NYS PERB Contracts - Disc 26 - 09/14-02/15 (Box 433)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 1 (Box 434)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 2 (Box 435)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 3 (Box 436)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 3 (Box 437)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 4 (Box 438)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 5 (Box 439)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 6 (Box 440)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 7 (Box 441)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 8 (Box 442)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 9 (Box 443)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 10 (Box 444)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 11 (Box 445)
- NYS PERB CBA Disc 12 (Box 446)
- NYS PERB BD Decisions -- 2013 + 2014 (Box 447)
- NYS PERB Contracts Disc 27 (Box 448)
- NYS PERB Contracts Disc 28 (Box 449)
- NYS PERB Contracts Disc 29-1 (Box 450)
- NYS PERB Contracts Disc 29-2 (Box 451)
- NYS PERB Contracts Disc 30 (Box 452)
- NYS PERB Contracts Disc 31 (Box 453)
  - NYS PERB Contracts Disc 31 (Box 453, Folder 1)